(Leonard:)Oh, I took care of it.
(Amy:), we are live
(Amy:)in five,
four, three...
(Amy:)Oh, wait. Oh, shoot,
I already pushed the button.
(Amy:)Never mind, we're live.
(Sheldon:)Uh, hello
(Sheldon:)and welcome to a
special live edition
of Dr. Sheldon Cooper...
and Dr. Amy Farrah Fowler
present...
Dr. Sheldon Cooper's
Fun With Flags.
(Amy:)Consider tonight's episode
(Amy:)a Valentine's Day gift
for you, our viewers.
(Sheldon:)It's also my gift to you.
That was clear, right?
'Cause you're not
getting anything else.
(Amy:)Since we're live,
(Amy:)you'll finally
be able to reach out to us
(Amy:)with your flag thoughts
and flag questions.
(Sheldon:)Allow us to answer a few quick
ones that we get all the time.
(Sheldon:)Uh, uh, yes, I
really am a doctor.
(Sheldon:)Uh, yes, she really
is my girlfriend.
(Amy:)No, I just blink a lot,
(Amy:)it's not Morse code
for "rescue me."